cdrinfo.com 2006-12-05

# Privacy Statement for CdrInfo.com

| 

**Privacy Statement for CDRInfo.COM **

CDR Info has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: CDR Info.COM 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is not shared with other companies. We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does not use cookies. We do not have access to any information about you from cookies you might receive while visiting our site. CDRInfo works with a third party that hosts our e-mail newsletters and serves ads into this publication. 

To find out more about how [AdTegrity](http://www.adtegrity.com/) manages the privacy of information in conjunction with hosting and serving ads into our newsletters, please visit this [**link**](http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp) **.**

**Public Forums  
**This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security  
**This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.) 

**Choice/Opt-Out  
**Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send us email by submitting the form at this page

**Correct/Update  
**This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Email us here

**Contacting the Web Site  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by submitting the form at this page. 

* * *

Third Party Advertising 

We use BUDS INC, MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

* * *

##### Preserving our Users' Privacy

CdrInfo.com is poised into helping all our users preserve their own on-line privacy. We take any incident communicated to us very seriously and we investigate it thoroughly.

In any case, CdrInfo.com preserves the right to review by itself any non-open source advertisement code (non-javascript or non-html banners such as "rich media" like flash, shockwave, java, activeX, etc). In case an advertiser chooses not to conform with this peer reviewed, open code practice, CdrInfo.com can, at any time, terminate any related campaign, at no further advertiser notice, at the sole expenses of the offending advertiser and without any single refund!

|  |  [ **Octave  
CD DVD Duplicators** ](http://www.octave.com/)  
---  
[ **Primera DVD / CD  
Duplicators** ](http://www.primera.com/)  
[ **Primera Europe CD / DVD  
Duplizierer und Drucker** ](http://www.primeraeurope.com/)  
 **DVD CD Duplicators  
MF Digital**   
 **Microboards  
Disc Copiers/Printers**   
 **CD Duplicators  
DVD Duplicators by Disc Makers**   
 **Blank DVDs  
from Disc Makers**   
 **CD DVD Duplicators**   
**by Vinpower**   
 **Noble House CD & DVD**   
**Duplicators/Printers**
